<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!-- This document was created with Syntext Serna Free. -->
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" []>
<book>
  <bookinfo>
    <title>BabBot WoW Automa</title>
    <author>
      <firstname>ivp4</firstname>
      <surname/>
      <affiliation>
        <orgname/>
      </affiliation>
    </author>
    <author>
      <surname>tanis</surname>
    </author>
    <pubdate>November 29, 2009</pubdate>
  </bookinfo>
  <chapter>
    <title>Configure &amp; Run bot</title>
    <section>
      <title>System Requirements</title>
      <para>Some parameters are still hardcoded and will be editable during a
      later release. Right now you&apos;re required to run on a 32bit OS (XP or
      Vista). Development releases for x64 processors are under testing. You
      can still compile it in 64bit mode from the sources though. </para>
      <para>In order to run, BabBot requires to be run from a user with
      administrator privileges so that it can run the WoW client as a guest
      user (currently the username is &quot;guest&quot; and it&apos;s got to be enabled in
      your OS). </para>
      <section>
        <title>OS</title>
        <para>BabBot has been tested on the following platforms:

    </para>
        <para>* Windows XP 32-bit
    </para>
        <para>* Windows Vista 32-bit
    </para>
        <para>* Windows XP 64-bit
    </para>
        <para>* Windows Vista 64-bit 

</para>
        <para>The current development version is under testing for:

    </para>
        <para>* Windows 7 32-bit
    </para>
        <para>* Windows 7 64-bit </para>
      </section>
      <section>
        <title>Privileges</title>
        <para>In order to run BabBot it&apos;s necessary to have administrator privileges for the account running BabBot itself. This is because the bot will instantiate WoW&apos;s client as the guest user.

</para>
        <para><emphasis role="italic">Guest user has to be enabled in your OS. </emphasis></para>
      </section>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Basic usage </title>
      <para>Run BabBot and launch WoW through the &quot;Run WoW&quot; button. If your copy of WoW has been installed properly, BabBot will detect its path and use it. Otherwise you&apos;ll have to set it in the Options menu.</para>
      <para>If you&apos;ve enabled autologin in the Options, BabBot will use your credentials to log into the game directly, otherwise you will have to log in by hand.

</para>
      <para><emphasis role="italic">Make sure that you have enabled &quot;Click to move&quot; and &quot;Auto-loot&quot; in WoW or some features might not work as expected. </emphasis></para>
      <para>If it&apos;s the first time you&apos;re running BabBot, you will want to make a new profile to start with. Enter a name and a description in the fields you see on the Main tab and then select the WayPoints? tab. Make sure that &quot;Normal&quot; is selected in the dropdown list and check &quot;Auto add waypoints&quot;. Now start moving to record the path your bot will walk through during its farming cycle. When you are done, uncheck &quot;Auto add waypoints&quot;.

</para>
      <para>Now it&apos;s time to choose which mobs we will attack. So select the &quot;Enemies&quot; tab. Run around the path you made before and target the mobs you want to kill by selecting them and clicking on the &quot;Add to list&quot; button. You don&apos;t need to add each mob as BabBot will attack any mob that has the same name as those you have put into the list.

</para>
      <para>Once you are done, it&apos;s time to save your work so that you don&apos;t have to do it again when you shutdown the bot. Just click on the &quot;Main&quot; tab and click &quot;Save&quot; and choose a filename for your profile. When you run the bot again you will be able to load your profile with the &quot;Load&quot; button.

</para>
      <para>The next step is to load a script. A script is a collection of commands that your bot will execute in order to perform things like farming, grinding, walking around, sell stuff, repairs, etc..

</para>
      <para>BabBot comes with a sample script that has been written based on the Paladin class. Anyone can take that script and modify it and customize it for any other class.

</para>
      <para>So, for the time being, just load the example script by clicking on &quot;Load&quot; on the Main tab under the &quot;Script&quot; group, browse to the scripts folder, enter the Paladin folder and select Core.cs

</para>
      <para>BabBot will load the script and be ready to start. It&apos;s time to click on the &quot;Start&quot; button and enjoy watching your bot doing its duties. </para>
    </section>
  </chapter>
  <chapter>
    <title>Configure Talent Template</title>
    <section>
      <title>Import from WoW Armory site</title>
      <para/>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>Manual adjustment</title>
      <para/>
    </section>
  </chapter>
</book>
